[music]
I think the greatest thing about the
role that I have is that we get to speak
to 20,000 customers a day. And I think
that's obviously a huge privilege, but
it comes with great responsibility.
Every call is unique and every caller is
unique. We're really here to help people
in their day-to-day lives.
>> Is a very human-driven business both in
terms of the clientele we deal with, but
also in terms of the experience I have
myself in my roles.
>> Just to be uh this company that can
bring some comfort to the client, it's
something that I don't think has a price
on it. Knowing that your your family
will be okay.
Coming to Montreal is like coming home
in a lot of ways. There's uh
I have colleagues who went from
disability to um sales teams. If you're
interested in something, you can reach
out. Our manager always tells us,
"Listen, if you see something like that
that might peique your interest, let me
know.
And the training that is provided here,
the tool that they give you to be
successful at your job is priceless. We
feel supported and this is something
that we really value.
>> There's a lot of care put into the
training [music] and I was able to to
bond with my teammates.
But if you're certainly willing to grow
as an individual, if you're willing to
continue to have great human
connections, [music] and if you're
willing to be in a place that truly is
obsessed about their customers, then
then this is something that I think you
would really enjoy. A better career
starts here.